

### **OBJECTIVE**

As a game developer, I understand how mechanics can make or break the gameplay experience. As a designer and web developer, I know what a clean, responsive interface can do for your business. I enjoy technical aspects of design & development and polishing critical details that others may overlook. I am fully confident in proving what I say I can do. Contact me and let's work together.

#### **EDUCATION**

# University of Richmond | Richmond, Virginia | 2019

Currently Enrolled in the Coding Bootcamp managed by Trilogy Education Graduating in October, 2019

- Studying full-stack development, API integration and databasing
- Studying command line interface and git version-control on GitHub

## Longwood University | Farmville, Virginia | 2014 -2018

Majored in Graphic Design & Animation with a Bachelors of Fine Arts Graduated on May 19th, 2018

- Studied design elements, principles, visual problem solving, branding & production
- Studied 3D modeling, rigging, animation, texturing & rendering
- Created a fully-playable game in Unity called "TILT" for my senior project
- Member of LAS (Lancer Animation Studios) & the 3D Modeling Club

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Target | Midlothian, Virginia | Oct 2018 - Jan 2019

Flexible Fulfillment

- Shopped for online orders and in-store pickups for arriving customers
- Packed and prepared orders for UPS transit

## Kroger | Midlothian, Virginia | May 2016 - Feb 2017

Clicklist Attendant

- Shopped for online orders and prepared groceries for arriving customers
- Finalized customer payments car-side & loaded their groceries for them

#### **SKILLS & CAPABILITIES**

Game development pipeline

Full-stack web development with API integration & databasing Command line interface & git version-control Vector creation, image manipulation & motion graphics 3D modeling, rigging, animation, texturing & rendering Leadership, teamwork & logical problem solving KISS & DRY principles

Chesterfield, Virginia ericpowell777@gmail.com ericpowell3d.com Find Me On: **FAVORED TOOLS** C#/Unity Engine HTML/CSS **JavaScript** Node.js GitBash/CLI Adobe CC Blender/Maya Logic Pro Office

<sup>\*</sup>Please visit my portfolio site <u>ericpowell3d.com</u> for more detailed information